maersksealand.com 2017-06-09

# Privacy and Cookie Policy | Maerskline Terms

This website is provided and controlled by Maersk Line A/S, Esplanaden 50, DK-1098 Copenhagen K, Denmark, CVR no.: 22 75 62 14 (“Maersk”).

##  1\. Scope 

Maersk recognizes and respects the importance of the privacy of our visitors of our websites. This policy accounts for the personal data and cookies etc. used via our websites. If you do not agree with the terms herein, please do not use this website and delete the cookies placed by the website.

Please be aware that a separate privacy statement applies to recruitment. The privacy state-ment applicable to recruitment is available [here](http://www.maersk.com/Career/Vacancies/Pages/PrivacyStatement_EN.aspx). However, the section on cookies below also applies to recruitment.

##  2.  Personal data

On our websites, we may collect information about name, postal address, email address, other contact information, age, interests, gender, IP addresses and other personal data. Our websites are intended for a general audience, and Maersk does not knowingly collect personal data about any person under the age of 18 years.

We process personal data for the following purposes:

  * Provision of Maersk services and products and to accommodate your requests and inquiries
  * Provision of newsletters offered by Maersk
  * The purposes listed in the below cookie section

As a global group Maersk may transfer personal data collected by us on an aggregated or individual level to various divisions, subsidiaries, joint ventures and affiliated companies of A.P. Møller – Mærsk A/S (“Maersk Group”) around the world located inside or outside the European Economic Area for the purposes stated above, as well to data processors outside of Maersk in India or other countries globally for storage and service purposes. Personal data will not be disclosed to anyone outside the Maersk Group without your consent unless permitted or required under applicable legislation.

We delete or anonymize your personal data when it is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected and subsequently processed.

If you have submitted personal data to us, e.g. when registering for a newsletter, you enjoy certain rights to access and rectify data, however, subject to certain legal limitations.

We have implemented appropriate organizational and technical security measures to protect your personal data. We store personal data on servers with limited access located in secured facilities, and our security measures are evaluated on an ongoing basis. The servers are protected by anti-virus software and firewalls, among other measures.

##  3.  Cookies 

Our websites use cookies. A cookie is a small text file, which is stored on your computer in order to recognize your computer at recurring visits. The cookie may transmit information via your browser with a purpose of authenticating or identifying the computer (via e.g. the IP address) or the user. Cookies may contain information such as registration data and user preferences. When a server receives a request from a computer which stores a cookie from the website, the server is able to use the information stored in the cookie in combination with the information stored on the server. A cookie cannot collect information from your computer and cannot carry any vira or other damaging files.

The following third parties store the following cookies on this website:

  * Google Analytics and Google DoubleClick (provided by Google Inc.) and Eloqua (provided by Eloqua Limited) to enable us a) to perform statistical analyses of e.g. number of visitors, information on gender, age, location, interests and the like to learn about our visitors and b) to improve the website friendliness and usability, e.g. on the basis of website traffic measurements
  * Addthis (provided by AddThis, Inc.) to enable the visitors of our website to use social media features, like sharing, sending or recommending pages toothers
  * Youtube (provided by YouTube LLC.) to store session preferences (e.g. language) and suggest other content based on your previous uses (only activated when you are logged in to Youtube when visiting our website and only when clicking the YouTube button)
  * Facebook (provided by Facebook, Inc.) to identify users logged in to Facebook for the purpose of sharing content on Facebook (only when you are logged in to Facebook when visiting our website and only when clicking the Facebook button)
  * LinkedIn (provided by LinkedIn Corp.) and Eloqua (provided by Eloqua Limited) to enable us a) to enable the “follow” and “share” features of LinkedIn (only when you are logged in to LinkedIn when visiting our website and only when clicking the LinkedIn button), and b) to perform statistical analyses of information on business demographics to learn about our visitors
  * Multiview (provided by Multiview, Inc.) to aggregate anonymous visitor information about the audience that visits the Maersk Line website and provide Maersk Line with insight that allows the improvement of digital marketing relevance.

You may delete cookies if you no longer wish to store them on your computer. However, please note that the high quality of our website may be reduced as a consequence thereof. Please refer to the help guide for your browser for further guidance.

  * For Internet Explorer, a help guide is available [here](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies)
  * For Mozilla, a help guide is available [here](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)
  * For Chrome, a help guide is available [here](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)
  * For Safari, a help guide is available [here](http://support.apple.com/kb/ph5042)

##  4.  Changes 

We reserve the right in our sole discretion to amend and/or delete this privacy and cookie policy at any time without providing prior notice to you. We will post the at any time current version of this privacy and cookie policy on the website.

##  5.  Contact details 

If you have any questions or comments or wish to exercise your rights under applicable legislation, please contact our privacy team by emailing to [dataprivacy@maersk.com](mailto:dataprivacy@maersk.com).

##  6\.  Law and jurisdiction 

These terms shall be subject to Danish law and any dispute, claim, matter of construction or interpretation arising out of or relating to the website, including these terms, shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Danish courts.
